so like we all love girl groups right whether it's destiny's child whether it is en vogue
free your mind whether it's swv or escape and it's a whole different world with the girl group
dynamics okay i mean we just saw notori and aid adrian bylan make up and they go way back to the
cheetah girls oh what's the three other to the three lw okay girl group dynamics is a real thing
and it is something i'm very curious about which is why i had candy barras of escape on small doses
this week talking about girl group dynamics if you've been watching her show swv and escape queens
of r&b then you know that the girl group dynamics is a thing it's a thing so if you're as curious as i
am then you need to get on the good foot all right you can check it out everywhere podcasts are casted
and you can also watch side effects of girl group dynamics with candy barras on youtube at amandaseals
tv and let me just tell you watching and listening two different experiences both amazing so make time